So hello guys, welcome to your
lovely YouTube channel, so let's start
this video, there is a disclaimer, guys you must be able to
see this disclaimer, so let's start the
video, you must be able to see that if we
talk about Larson True, then
brother, he has won the order, that is,
he has got a good contract
and there is Torrent Energy Storage Solution,
so
he has got a good contract from them, so you must be able to see that if we
see, for whom he has got it, then he has got this project to develop the APAM
Store Storage Right Storage Facility.  That means
this project has been received for construction.
You guys might be able to see.  So
you must be able to see that 3000 MW
Shadongar One Pump Storage Project in
Raigad Maharashtra.
Then look further,
how much is this project going to cost?  So you can see
that its value is going to remain between Rs 2500 crore to Rs 5000 crore.  If we
talk about this project, then you must be able to
see that if we talk about ICICI LBD
General Insurance Company,
we will talk about their quarter 3 results of FI 26.
So you guys must be able to see that the company has got
good quarter 3 results.
Look, let us talk about gross direct premium income.
So you can see that if
we look inside it,
a good increase of 13.33% has been seen.
So how much has that been?  So it is 741 crores.
Then if we look further, if we
talk about net premium, then
how much net premium has the company earned, then an
increase of 12.6% has been seen in that too.  So
how much has that been?  So it has been ₹5685 crores.
So if we compare it with the previous year, we can
see a significant increase.
You guys might be able to see that.  Then let us
talk about total income, that is, look at the total revenue, you
can see that the revenue from operations is
₹610 crore.   If we
look inside that also, we can see a year on
year increase of 12.4%.  So, the
results have been quite good.  Then if we
talk about profitability, if we talk about the profit of the company, if we talk about
net profit, then you
people must be able to see that the company has made a profit of ₹658 crores.  If we
talk about quarter 326, then if
we compare it with the quarter of last year, then
you will be able to see that a decline of 9.06% has been
seen.  That means there has been a
decline in profit.
You guys might be able to see that.  If
we talk about our renewable technology, that is, the
company which is our energy sub-contract, they have got that
contract.  So for whom is
this contract given?  So now those people are going to do
construction.
Now they have got a ground mounted solar power project of 25 MW to 35 MW.
Right?  So how much is this project going to be worth
?  So if we talk about this project which is going to be worth ₹12 crores, then
what will those people do?  So they will do
construction, procurement
and engineering related work.   That
means, this power plant project is a
solar power plant project, they have
got a contract of ₹12
crores, you might be able to see that.  Then if
we talk about Raghav and Productivity N Enhancer, then
brother, if we look at the revenue of the company, that is,
we are going to discuss the
quarter 3 result of Raghav Productivity Enhancer of F26, then you people must be able to
see that the revenue from operations has been Rs
64.49 crore.  So if we
look inside that also, we can
see a year on year increase of 17.17%.
Then if we talk about net profit,
you can see that the
net profit has been Rs 14.12 crore.  If we look inside that also, then we can
see a good increase of 43.93%.  If
we compare it with the previous year's quarter,
then if we talk about earnings per
share, it is ₹3.08.
So a good
increase is being seen in that too.  Look, if
we talk about 5 Paisa Capital, then
look at their quarter 3 result of 26, if we
talk about total income, it was Rs 79.34
crore.  So if we look at 2.6%, we have seen a quarter
on quarter increase.  And if you
look at it year on year, you will see that there has been a
decline of 7%.  Then if
we talk about profit after tax, the
company has made a profit of Rs 12.383 crore.
So if we look quarter on
quarter, we have seen an increase of 29%
and year on year we can see that there is a
decline of 24%.  Then if we
talk about earnings per share, we can see
that the company has earned ₹3.93.  If
we look at the earnings per share, the
company's rate is ₹3.93.  So let us look at it quarter on
quarter, that is, let
us compare it with the previous share quarter on quarter.
So you must be able to see that it has resulted in a decree.
Then let us talk about Tokyoplast
International and look at the
consolidated revenue of the company for quarter 326, it has been Rs
17.14 crore.  If we
look inside it, we can see a decline of 10.02%.  If
we compare with the previous year's quarters, then let's
talk about more consolidated, brother.  Ah, if
we talk about profit, then overall the
company has made a loss.  You people must be able to
see that the company has incurred losses.
No profit has been made.  Whether the company has not made any
profit or loss.  So guys,
in today's video,
we will end with this.  If you liked this video then please
like, share
and subscribe to this video.  Thanks
for watching this video.